A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39; 234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
  - Education, 1987-1991; 12; 44.01 Cubic Feet 70 letter document boxes and 37 legal document boxes
    - Colleges, 2
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Program in Science and Technology for International Security (Box 208, Folder 7, Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Meharry Medical College - Cousins (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Middlebury College (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Middlebury College - Cousins (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine - Fundraising (Box 217, Folder 2-3)
      - New York University (NYU) - A-Z (Box 218, Folder 1-2)
      - New York University (NYU) - A-Z - Cousins (Box 214, Folder 4-5)
      - New York University (NYU) - Center for War, Peace and the News Media (Box 214, Folder 6, Box 215, Folder 1-3, Box 216)
      - North Carolina State University (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Pace University (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Pace University - Cousins (Box 221, Folder 1)
      - Pace University - School of Law (Box 221, Folder 2)
      - Pacific School of Religion (Box 219, Folder 1)
      - Pacific School of Religion - Cousins (Box 221, Folder 3)
      - Pacific School of Religion - Printed Matter (Box 219, Folder 2)
      - Portland State University - Cousins (Box 221, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University (Box 219, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - A-B (Box 219, Folder 4-5)
      - Princeton University - C-Z (Box 220, Folder 1-6)
      - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies (Box 221, Folder 5-6, Box 222, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Art Museum (Box 223, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Board of Trustees (Box 223, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Center for Human Values (University Center for Human Values) (Box 223, Folder 3-4, Box 224, Folder 1-2)
      - Princeton University - Center for Human Values (University Center for Human Values) - A-Z (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Center for Human Values (University Center for Human Values) - Tanner Lectures (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Contributions (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Contributions - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Contributions - A-Z (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller -Contributions - Annual Giving - JY Ranch, 1975-1983 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - General (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Princeton University - Printed Matter (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - Princeton University - School of Engineering/Applied Science (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - School of Engineering-Applied Sciences - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs (Box 226, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 4)
      - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (Box 226, Folder 3)
      - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 5)
      - Spelman College (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - Spelman College - Search for President (Box 222, Folder 6)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) (Box 227, Folder 2)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 7)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) - Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy (Box 227, Folder 3)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government (Box 227, Folder 4-5, Box 228, Folder 1-2)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 8)
      - Syracuse University (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - Syracuse University - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Union Theological Seminary (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Union Theological Seminary - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 10)
      - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia (Box 228, Folder 5)
      - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 9)
      - United Negro College Fund (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - United Negro College Fund - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 11)
      - Universidad de las Americas-Puebla (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - University of California (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - University of California - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 12)
      - University of California, San Francisco School of Medicine (Box 229, Folder 4-5)
      - University of Cape Town Fund, Inc. (Box 229, Folder 6)
      - University of Chicago (Box 230, Folder 1-2)
      - University of Chicago - A-Z (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - University of Chicago - A-Z - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 13)
      - University of Chicago - Centennial Celebration (Box 230, Folder 4, Box 231, Folder 1)
      - University of Chicago - Divinity School (Box 231, Folder 2-3)
      - University College Dublin (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - University of Edinburgh (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - University of Edinburgh - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 14)
      - University of Florida (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - University of Lethbridge, Alberta, Canada (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - University of London - London School of Economics and Political Science (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - University of Louisville, Louisville, Kentucky (Box 232, Folder 3-4)
      - University of Louisville - Cousins (Box 222, Folder 15)
      - University of Louisville - Joe Elkes (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - University of Maine (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - University of Maine System (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - University of Maryland (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - University of Maryland - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - University of Massachusetts (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - University of Massachusetts - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - University of Miami (Box 233, Folder 6)
      - University of Michigan (Box 233, Folder 7)
      - University of Minnesota (Box 233, Folder 8)
      - University of Minnesota - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - University of Notre Dame (Box 233, Folder 9)
      - University of Notre Dame - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - University of Oklahoma (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - University of Pennsylvania (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - University of Pittsburgh (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - University of Rochester (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - University of Southern California (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - University of Sussex - Cousins (Box 234, Folder 6)
      - University of Texas, Austin (Box 235, Folder 6)
      - University of Texas System (Box 235, Folder 7)
      - University of Vermont (Box 235, Folder 8)
      - University of Vermont - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - University of Virginia (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - University of Virginia - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Vassar College (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Vassar College - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Vermont Law School (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - World College West (Box 236, Folder 4-5)
      - World College West - Printed Material (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Yale University (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Yale University - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Yale University - A-Z (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Student Service, 3
      - Foreign Student Service - A-Z (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Student Service - A-Z - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, 4
      - Foundations - A-D (Box 237, Folder 5-7)
      - Foundations - E-M (Box 239, Folder 1-5)
      - Foundations - M-Z (Box 240, Folder 1-3)
      - Foundations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 238, Folder 6-11)
      - Aga Khan Foundation (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Joseph Campbell Foundation (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Winston Churchill Foundation of the United States (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Winston Churchill Travelling Fellowship Foundation (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Coast Guard Foundation (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Fetzer Foundation (Box 241, Folder 4-5, Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Fetzer Foundation - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - Foundation for Community Encouragement (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Foundation for Community Encouragement - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - Fundacion Luis Munoz Marin (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - The Jefferson Educational Foundation (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - The Leakey Foundation (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Manitou Foundation (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - George C. Marshall Foundation (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Threshold Foundation (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - A-N (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - N-Z (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - By-Laws (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Finances (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - Dewitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - A-Z (Box 245, Folder 2-3)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Finances (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1990 (Box 246, Folder 1-2)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 246, Folder 3)
      - Wallace Funds (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - Wallace Funds - Board of Directors - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - Wallace Funds - A-Z (Box 247, Folder 1-2)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1989 (Box 247, Folder 3)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 4)
      - Wallace Funds - Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Historical Societies, 5
      - Historical Societies - A-Z (Box 248, Folder 2-4)
      - Historical Societies - F-Z - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 4-5)
      - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - National Maritime Historical Society (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - National Maritime Historical Society - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 6)
      - New York Historical Society (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - New York Historical Society - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 7)
      - St. Croix Landmarks Society, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Historical Society (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Housing, 6
      - International Houses - A-Z (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - International House, Berkeley, CA (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - International House, Chicago, Illinois (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - International House, New York City (Box 251, Folder 4-5)
      - International House, New York City - A-Z (Box 251, Folder 6)
      - International House, New York City - Contributions (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - International House, New York City - Fundraising (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Radio/Television, 7
      - Radio-Television - A-P (Box 252, Folder 3-8)
      - Radio-Television - Q-Z (Box 253, Folder 1-2)
      - Radio-Television - A-I - Cousins (Box 249, Folder 8-11)
      - Radio-Television - J-Z - Cousins (Box 257, Folder 1-4)
      - Center for Communications (Box 253, Folder 3-4)
      - Center for Communications - Cousins (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Cousins (Box 257, Folder 6, Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Contributions (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting - Cousins (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Foundation for Global Broadcasting - Cousins (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Millenium (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Orbit Productions (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Press and Public Project - Cousins (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Public Interest Video Network (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Twin Cities Public Television (KTCA) (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - WETA, 2 envelopes (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - WETA - Cousins (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Schools, 8
      - Schools - A-H (Box 255, Folder 1-5)
      - Schools - I-M (Box 256, Folder 1-2)
      - Schools - N-S (Box 260, Folder 1-4)
      - Schools - T-Z (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Schools - A-P - Cousins (Box 259, Folder 4-13)
      - Schools - Q-Z - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 1-3)
      - American Academy in Rome (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Bank Street College of Education (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Chapin School, New York City (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Colorado Rocky Mountain School, Inc. - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Elementary School Center, New York, NY (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Good Hope School, St. Croix, V.I (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Harlem School of the Arts (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Harlem School of the Arts - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - Hurricane Island Outward Bound School (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Hurricane Island Outward Bound School - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 6)
      - Juilliard School (Box 263, Folder 1)
      - The Madeira School, Greenway, Va (Box 263, Folder 2)
      - The Madeira School, Greenway, Va - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 7)
      - St. Aloysius Education Clinic (Box 265, Folder 8)
      - St. John School of the Arts (Box 263, Folder 3)
      - School for Field Studies (Box 263, Folder 4)
      - Skowhegan School of Paintings and Sculpture (Box 263, Folder 5)
      - Skowhegan School of Paintings and Sculpture - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Energy, 1987-1991; 13; 3.8 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes
    - Energy - A-B (Box 264, Folder 1-2)
    - Energy - L-Z (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Energy - A - Cousins (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Energy - B-N - Cousins (Box 266, Folder 1-5)
    - Energy - O-Z - Cousins (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - American Energy Assurance Council (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Center for Renewable Resources (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Association for Sound Energy (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Hanford Education Action League (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Energy and Environmental Research (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Ladakh Solar Project (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Ladakh Solar Project - Cousins (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Nuclear Reform Project (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Radioactive Waste Campaign (Box 270, Folder 1-2)
    - Resource Center (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Rocky Mountain Institute (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Safe Energy Communication Council (Box 271, Folder 2-3)
    - Safe Energy Resource Center, Inc. - Cousins (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Snake River Alliance (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee Valley Energy Coalition - Cousins (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - The Tides Foundation (Box 272, Folder 4, Box 273, Folder 1)
  - F-I, 1987-1991; 14; 5.97 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
    - F - Miscellaneous (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - G - Miscellaneous (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Geriatrics - A-Z (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - H - Miscellaneous (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Affairs - A-Z (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Hispanic Affairs - A-Z - Cousins (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - General (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - A-Z (Box 274, Folder 1-4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Annandale (Box 274, Folder 5, Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Annual Reports (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Board of Trustees (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Contributions (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Dobkin. John H. (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Finances, 1989-1991 (Box 276, Folder 1-4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Finances, 1988 (Box 277, Folder 1-2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Finances - Cambridge Associates (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - General (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Event, 1991 November (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Kykuit Event, 1991 June (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Dinner Dance Gala, 1990 October 30 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Rainbow Room Gala, 1989 November 13 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Kykuit Event, 1989 June 4 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Rainbow Room Dinner Dance, 1988 November 14 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - "Midsummer's Evening" Dinner Dance at Sunnyside, 1988 July 27 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Fundraising - Gala Dinner at the Plaza, 1987 November 2 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Greenways in the Hudson River Valley (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Meetings/Minutes, 1991 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Meetings/Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 280, Folder 1-4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Meetings/Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 281, Folder 1-4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Montgomery Place (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Printed Matter (Box 282, Folder 3, Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Union Church of Pocantico Hills - Soundview Preparatory School (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Horticulture - A-Z (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Horticulture - A-Z - Cousins (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Horticulture - Brooklyn Botanic Garden (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Horticulture - Ida Cason Callaway Foundation and Callaway Gardens (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Horticulture - Horticultural Society of New York, Inc. (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Horticulture - National Peace Garden (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - National Peace Garden - Cousins (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden (Box 284, Folder 2-4)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden - Cousins (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Horticulture - Old Westbury Gardens (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - IBEC (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - International Relations, 1987-1991; 15; 27.34 Cubic Feet 72 letter document boxes
    - International Relations - A-Z, 1
      - International Relations - A-F (Box 285, Folder 3-6)
      - International Relations - C - Cousins (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - International Relations - G-N (Box 286, Folder 1-5)
      - International Relations - O-Z (Box 287, Folder 1-3)
      - International Relations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 288, Folder 1-8)
      - Alerdinck Foundation (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - American Austrian Foundation, Inc. (Box 287, Folder 4)
      - American Committee on U.S. Soviet Relations (Box 289, Folder 2-3, Box 290, Folder 1)
      - American European Community Association (Box 287, Folder 5)
      - Amnesty International USA (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - Atlantic Council (Box 292, Folder 1)
      - British American Security Information Council (Box 292, Folder 2)
      - British American Security Information Council - Cousins (Box 290, Folder 3)
      - Children's Art Exchange (Box 290, Folder 4)
      - Citizens Fund (Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Council on Ocean Law (Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Council for United States and Italy (Box 292, Folder 3)
      - The Eisenhower World Affairs Institute (Box 291, Folder 2)
      - The English Speaking Union (Box 292, Folder 4)
      - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders on Human Survival (Box 292, Folder 5)
      - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders on Human Survival - Cousins (Box 291, Folder 3)
      - Institute for Defense and Disarmament Studies (Box 291, Folder 4)
      - Institute for East-West Security Studies (Box 293, Folder 1-2)
      - Institute for East-West Security Studies - Cousins (Box 295, Folder 1-2)
      - Institute for Soviet-American Relations (Box 295, Folder 3)
      - Interaction Council (Box 293, Folder 3)
      - International Foundation for Education and Self-Help (Box 296, Folder 1)
      - International Foundation for the Survival and Development of Humanity (Box 293, Folder 4)
      - International Foundation for the Survival and Development of Humanity - Cousins (Box 296, Folder 2)
      - International Human Development Project (Box 293, Folder 5)
      - International Institute for Strategic Studies (Box 293, Folder 6)
      - International Rescue Committee, Inc. (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - Internews Network (Box 294, Folder 2)
      - Internews Network - Cousins (Box 296, Folder 3-4)
      - North American Institute (Box 294, Folder 3)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) (Box 294, Folder 4)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) - Cousins (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies (Box 297, Folder 2-3, Box 298, Folder 1)
      - Spanish Institute (Box 294, Folder 5)
      - World Affairs Council of Inland Southern California (Box 298, Folder 2)
      - World Centre (Box 299, Folder 1)
      - World Service (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Countries/Continents, 2
      - Afghanistan - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 2)
      - Africa - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 3)
      - Africa - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 298, Folder 4-5)
      - Africa - African American Institute (Box 299, Folder 4)
      - Africa - African American Institute - Cousins (Box 298, Folder 6)
      - Asia - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 5)
      - Asia - A-Z - Cousins (Box 298, Folder 7)
      - Asia - Asia Society (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - Asia - Asia Society - A-Z (Box 300, Folder 2)
      - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions (Box 300, Folder 3)
      - Asia - Asian Cultural Council (Box 300, Folder 4)
      - Asia - East-West Center Foundation (Box 300, Folder 5, Box 301, Folder 1-4)
      - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Annual Reports (Box 302, Folder 1)
      - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Fundraising (Box 302, Folder 2)
      - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Meetings, 1987-1990 (Box 302, Folder 3-4)
      - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Printed Material (Box 302, Folder 5, Box 303, Folder 1-3, Box 304, Folder 1-2)
      - Australia - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 3)
      - Austria - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 4)
      - Brazil (Box 304, Folder 5)
      - Burma - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 6)
      - Canada - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 7)
      - Chile - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 8)
      - China (Box 305, Folder 1)
      - China - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 1)
      - China - America China Society (Box 305, Folder 2)
      - China - National Committe on United States China Relations (Box 305, Folder 3)
      - Costa Rica - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 4)
      - Cuba - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 5)
      - Ecuador (Box 305, Folder 6)
      - El Salvador (Box 305, Folder 7)
      - El Salvador - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 2)
      - Ethiopia - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 8)
      - France - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 9)
      - France - American Committee on the French Revolution (Box 306, Folder 1)
      - France - French-American Foundation (Box 306, Folder 2)
      - France - Institut Charles de Gaulle (Box 306, Folder 3)